Friedlander, Walter A.; Papers ger003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Miscellaneous materials, 8; 276 folders
  - Miscellaneous book and serial publications, 8.3; 45 folders.
    - Books and pamphlets, Undated; 8.3.1
      - Die internationale Organisation der sozialistischen Jugend: Bericht des Sekretariats der internationalen Verbindung der sozialistischen Jugendorganisationen, (August 1907) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 4)
      - Schulkind und Jugendlicher, (1930) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 5)
      - Some Facts About Expellees in Germany 1952 (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 6)
      - Soziale Arbeit Heute, (1951) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 7)
      - Taschenbuch des Deutschen Archivs für Jugendwohlfahrt, (1929) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 8)
      - Busse-Wilson, Elisabeth.Die Frau und die Jugendbewegung, (1920) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 9)
      - Frauendiener, Fritz.Der Gestaltwandel der staatlichen Jugendfürsorge, (1937) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 10)
      - Freud, Sigmund.Die Zukunft einer Illusion, (1927) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 11)
      - Seldte, Franz.Sozialpolitik im Dritten Reich, (1937) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 12)
      - Tepp, Max.Die neue Schule, (1919) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 13)
      - Wex, Else.Die Entwicklung der Sozialen Fürsorge in Deutschland (1914 bis 1927), (1929) (Box 45 (8.3.1-Books and pamphlets), Folder 14)
    - Serial publications (scattered issues), Undated; 8.3.2
      - ADA World, 1963-1966 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 15)
      - Amtsblatt der Stadt Berlin, 6 March 1933 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 16)
      - Aufbau (NY), 1 January 1937 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 17)
      - Blätter des Pestalozzi-Fröbel Verbandes, July-August 1965 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 18)
      - Council on Social Work Educationsional Record: Annette Rose Case, (1957) (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 19)
      - DIG-Informationen, 1974 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 20)
      - Deutschland-Berichte, 1937; 1978-1980 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 21)
      - eurosocial Newsletter, 1977 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 22)
      - Für Sie gelesen, 1964-1965 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 23)
      - Germany Today, 7 January 1946 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 24)
      - Inside Germany Reports, June 1942; April 1945 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 25)
      - International Council on Social Welfare.International Newsletter, (1972) (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 26)
      - Jüdische Wohlfahrtspflege und Sozialpolitik, December 1932 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 27)
      - Der Mensch in der sozialen Arbeit, 1933 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 28)
      - Mitteilungen der Arbeitsgemeinschaft für Jugendpflege und Jugendfürsorge, May 1966 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 29)
      - NASW News, 1970-1971 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 30)
      - The National Jewish Monthly, June 1964 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 31)
      - Near East Report, 15 October 1982 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 32)
      - Neues Beginnen, 1963 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 33)
      - Northern California Service League.Newsletter, 1969-1970 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 34)
      - Recht und Wirtschaft der Schule, April 1963 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 35)
      - RS-Briefe, October 1935-December 1937 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 36)
      - Social Work Journal, January 1950 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 37)
      - The Social Worker, 1967 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 38)
      - Der Sozialarbeiter, 1963-1976 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 39)
      - Sozialdemokrat Magazin, 1981 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 40)
      - Soziale Praxis, 1 December 1932 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 41)
      - SPD Auslandsbrief, 1972; 1974 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 42)
      - University of California.Faculty Bulletin, 1945 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 43)
      - The Welfare Record (Berkeley, CA), 1944-1945 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 44)
      - World Health, 1964 (Box 45 (8.3.2-Serial publications (scattered issues)), Folder 45)